windowspcguide.com 2019-05-18

# Privacy Policy

## **windowspcguide.com privacy policy**

 **WindowsPCGuide always respects your privacy.**

If you have any doubts about www.windowspcguide.com privacy policy feel free to www.windowspcguide.com/contact-us. We consider our blog visitors privacy is the most important point.

If you enter any personal information about you like your name, mobile number, address, email address and social media addresses in this website, Those personal information will not be revealed or sold or re entered any other ways of outside the blog.

 **Cookies and Web Beacons**

As you know cookies are used for storing the information about visitor choice.  Cookies itself doesn’t contain any personal information about visitors to the www.windowspcguide.com. Even though we do not use cookies on www.windowspcguide.com site to store your information.

 **External Websites**

www.windowspcguide.com is not responsible for information of external sites. We recommend you to read privacy policy of those sites. So, we are not responsible for that external sites content.

 **Credit Card Details  **

Our blog www.windowspcguide.com will never ask your personal credit or debit card details.  We promise you that we never cheat our blog visitors. If you find any inconvenience in www.windowspcguide.com blog feel free to bring to the Web Master.

 **Log Files & Double Click Dart Cookie :**

Log files generally contain information about your IP(internet protocol), browser type, referring or exit pages, number of clicks, date or stamp, ISP.  site administration, user demographic information. We(www.windowspcguide.com) do not use this Dart cooking or log files. But wait, we use third party advertisements on site to support or improve our site. These 3rd party party advertisers may use this Log files and Double click dart cookies.

These third party advertiser’s generally use this cookies to display the adds in website on visited user choice. So, to know the user preference Google use these cookies. www.windowspcguide.com do it’s level best secure your personal information.

If any other sites accessed through www.windowspcguide.com then you should must be aware of those websites privacy policies. We are not responsible for those sites privacy policies.

You can disable log files or double click dart cookies in your own browser or you can use programs to disable cookies.The URL is www.google.com/privacy_ads.html. If you have suggestions or queries please bring to WindowsPCGuide contact center.

 **Information Sharing and Disclosure  **

[ **WindowsPCGuide.com**](http://windowspcguide.com/) will not use, share, rent or sell your personal information with other people or non-affiliated programmes. Your personal information like mail address will not be made visible on website until you select to display.  

If you need any info E-mail to Web Master.

Thanks,

www.windowspcguide.com.
